question_data = [
        {"type": "boolean",
         "difficulty": "medium",
         "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Popcorn was invented in 1871 by Frederick W. Rueckheim in the USA where he sold the snack on the streets of Chicago.",
         "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Books",
         "question": "In Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, Hermione destroyed the fourth Horcrux by stabbing it with the Sword of Gryffindor.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History",
         "question": "During the Winter War, the amount of Soviet Union soliders that died or went missing was five times more than Finland&#039;s.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
         "question": "Klingons respect their disabled comrades, and those who are old, injuried, and helpless.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "In &quot;Super Mario World&quot;, the rhino mini-boss, Reznor, is named after the lead singer of the band &quot;Nine Inch Nails&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
         "question": "Nutcracker Suite was one of the musical pieces featured in Disney&#039;s 1940&#039;s film Fantasia.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "&quot;Foodfight!&quot; earned less than $80,000 at box office.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "The vapor produced by e-cigarettes is actually water.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Computers",
         "question": "The &#039;Raspberry Pi&#039; series of single-board computers were created in the United States.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "History",
         "question": "In 1967, a magazine published a story about extracting hallucinogenic chemicals from bananas to raise moral questions about banning drugs.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
         "question": "Kublai Khan is the grandchild of Genghis Khan?", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "The Ace Attorney trilogy was suppose to end with &quot;Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney &minus; Trials and Tribulations&quot; as its final game.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "The band STRFKR was also briefly known as Pyramiddd.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
         "question": "The character Plum from &quot;No Game No Life&quot; is a girl.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Animals",
                                          "question": "You can tell the age of a ladybird by counting the spots on his back.",
                                          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "The movie &quot;The Rocky Horror Picture Show&quot; (1975) opens with giant floating lips singing the opening song",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Books",
         "question": "The &quot;Berenstein Bears&quot; is the correct spelling of the educational children&#039;s book series&#039; name.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
         "question": "Klingons once had a period of Democracy in their history, they referred to it as the &quot;Dark Times&quot;.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Vehicles",
         "question": "In 1993 Swedish car manufacturer Saab experimented with replacing the steering wheel with a joystick in a Saab 9000.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "In the game &quot;Destiny,&quot; the three subclasses of the Hunter are Bladedancer, Nightstalker, and Sunsinger.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Computers",
         "question": "The open source program Redis is a relational database server.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                                          "question": "The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.",
                                          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History",
         "question": "The fourth funnel of the RMS Titanic was fake designed to make the ship look more powerful and symmetrical.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
         "question": "Druid is a mage class in &quot;Log Horizon&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
         "question": "In the 1988 film &quot;Akira&quot;, Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
                                           "question": "In the comic book &quot;Archie&quot;, Betty is friends with Veronica because she is rich.",
                                           "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History",
         "question": "The man that shot Alexander Hamilton was named Aaron Burr.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                                           "question": "In the periodic table, Potassium&#039;s symbol is the letter K.",
                                           "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
         "question": "There is a city called Rome in every continent on Earth.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                                          "question": "&quot;Neutral Milk Hotel&quot; is a real band.",
                                          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language &quot;Simlish&quot; was The Sims (2000).",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "History",
         "question": "Oxford University is older than the Aztec Empire. ", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                           "question": "Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
                                           "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "The word &quot;news&quot; originates from the first letters of the 4 main directions on a compass (North, East, West, South).",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "The National Animal of Scotland is the Unicorn.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                                           "question": "&quot;Cube&quot;, &quot;Cube 2: Hypercube&quot; and &quot;Cube Zero&quot; were directed by the same person.",
                                           "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
         "question": "The Neanderthals were a direct ancestor of modern humans.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                          "question": "Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.",
                                          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
         "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
         "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio&#039;s character hunts down the killer of his son.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "In the Resident Evil series, Leon S. Kennedy is a member of STARS.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "History",
                                          "question": "Augustus was the cousin of Julius Caesar. ",
                                          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
         "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klaang is a typical Klingon male.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
                                           "question": "The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
                                           "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
         "question": "&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                                          "question": "The 2010 film &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.",
                                          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
         "question": "Green Day&#039;s album &#039;American Idiot&#039; is considered a &quot;punk rock opera.&quot;",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
         "question": "Resident Evil 4 was originally meant to be a Nintendo GameCube exclusive.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
                                           "question": "Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis is a synonym for the disease known as silicosis.",
                                           "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
